

CONTACT ME AT

- 1927 Bowsprit Dr. Fort Collins, CO 80524
- jonpointer@msn.com
- ___ jonpointer.github.io/Portfolio/
- in linkedin.com/in/jon-pointerpe-5317619a/

SKILLS SUMMARY

- •••• Full Stack Web Development
- •••• HTML, CSS, JavaScript
- •••• jQuery, Node.js, React
- •••• Scientific Programming
- •••• Requirements Management
- • • Customer Interface

WORTH NOTING

- Self taught web developer plus Full Stack Bootcamp
- Experience managing difficult challenges including key customers
- Licensed Professional Engineer, 3 patents, and many publications

JON POINTER

FULL STACK WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Including full stack experience, my primary skill set is JavaScript programming including jQuery, Node.js, and React. With additional background in scientific programming and product development, I am a positive asset to a well rounded team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Principal Engineer - Technology Development

Woodward, Inc. | 2015 - present

- Responsible for advancing electromagnetic technologies within Woodward Industrial Systems for inclusion in product development projects.
- Create custom software tools and design guidelines to assist junior engineers in the development process.

Staff & Principal Engineer - Mechanical Development

Woodward, Inc. | 2005-2015

- Developed electromechanical actuators and valves for industrial customers.
- Lead project engineer and lead technical representative to primary customers.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

University of Denver

Full Stack Web Development Bootcamp | 2020-2021

- In depth study of the full breadth of tools and languages
- Exceptional individual and team projects accessible at GitHub

Colorado State University

BS & MS in Mechanical Engineering | 1996

- GPA: 3.5
- Focus on robotics and programming
- Activities included lab assistant and engineering clubs